Let us welcome last time final video of the section windows remote management will be calling
it as an bin arm very very I did not see this commands I did not see bin arm has been
involved in multiple instance in my experience.
So it was it was one of Microsoft service that will be that will be used to manage the hardware
and software under remote or target machine but hack us utilizing these features Microsoft
features and they will be using this bin arm to move laterally from one machine to
another machine.
You do not need to I will not suggest this kind of method everywhere the most of the
machines will not have a bin arm will not have a bin arm enabled there will be very very
huge steps you need to do to enable the bin arm because I followed a lot of steps before
not enable the bin arm even I have modified the network connection profile everything
ok.
So I will not suggest this step but it is one of really interesting one to notify and interesting
one to learn ok.
So basically bin arm stands for Windows remote management and it will be using a web based
service remotely it was using two of the port for high st dp 5985 and high st dps 5986 ok.
So once the attacker hijacked the credential from the credential access start is usually
the username and passwords.
So they have they have a lot of methods even RDP impact a library lot of impact library
for there but we have a windows remote management also.
So they will be using the windows remote management to get a consistent connection to get
more laterally from one machine to another machine.
So the step was really a simple one let me show you the step.
So you just needs to execute the evil bin arm that was defaultly coming in the Linux
Kali machine and I will be the target our windows machine and you will be the user and
T will be the password.
So before executing this command the user must be in the remote man user must be a remote
management user.
So here you can see he is an administrator and he is a remote management user right.
So user must be in a remote management user that is the essential thing that is an
essential thing here of in windows remote management okay.
So this is one of the powerful methods to do lateral movement from one machine to another
machine.
This is really used by the protectors to do something inside a machine okay.
But in less than 20% of the time less than 15% of the time I have seen they have used
the bin arm to communicate is that if they are using the bin arm.
So there will be a two ports has been involved 5984 and 5986.
This two ports if you check the network connections behind these two ports you can understand
there is something happening inside the bin arm okay.
So I hope you have a clear understanding about this concept body what we have seen till
now.
So also we have seen a bin arm here so you can you can see each privilege we have we have
an high mandatory level of revelations administrator level privilege and it's it's a pretty
simple so we don't need any third party applications to do that our calling machine default
has a bin arm tool so you can use the bin arm and you can utilize that and you can do
that okay.
So I hope you have a better understanding about the lateral movement how the attack will
be doing a lateral movement from one machine to another let's swap off from here we'll continue
discussion in the next video. For the next section, see you, bye-bye!